<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Apokatastasis</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Apokatastasis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.128.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 15:27:01 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>✏️ An Important Premise: The Inspiration of Scripture</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/bp-inspiration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 15:27:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/bp-inspiration/</guid>
      <description>Material Intro to the Hebrew Bible: Lecture 7
The Nature of the Bible Inspiration Origins of the Premise A very common attribution to the Scriptures that the church holds to is the premise of inspiration. Inspiration is a claim about the nature of the biblical texts. The meaning of this claim has had ongoing life in the history of the church and different traditions in different contexts and times have had varying understanings of what this means.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God is Breathing and So Are You</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/01-inspiration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 15:27:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/01-inspiration/</guid>
      <description>I do not mean to start this post aggressively but thoughtfully. I want to confront head on what the commonly accepted notions of inspiration mean for us today. I want to press into the questions that trouble a lot of people and to bring those into focus. I want to bring those notions and assumption into the light and question them. And I want to suggest an alternative lens for understanding inspiration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God is Breathing and So Are You</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/01-ot-lenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 17:54:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/01-ot-lenses/</guid>
      <description>The Word of God is inspired, inerrant, and infalliable. And when he was about eighteen years old, he grew a beard.
— Brad Jersak1
Research &amp;lsquo;When we come to to the bible expecting it to be an instructional manual intended by God to give us unwavering, cement hard certainty about our faith, we are actually creating problems for ourselves, beacues - as we I&amp;rsquo;ve come to see - the Bible wasn&amp;rsquo;t designed to meet that expectation.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
